[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tegestology is the hobby of collecting this.", "correct_answer": "Beer mats", "incorrect_answers": ["Coffee spoons", "Bottle labels", "Bottle lids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Raging Bull first hit the movie theatres?", "correct_answer": "1980", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1983", "1982"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much money does Evans get for a days work in 3:10 to Yuma when he hires out?", "correct_answer": "Two Dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["Eight Dollars", "Fifteen Dollars", "He doesnt hire out"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Moons shape is not quite round. What does it resemble?", "correct_answer": "Egg", "incorrect_answers": ["Kiwi", "Pear", "Lemon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the largest  eagle ever found on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Haasts Eagle", "incorrect_answers": ["Golden Eagle", "Harpy Eagle", "Bald Eagle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Albert Einstein asserted that the energy of a photon is proportional to what in his study of the photoelectronic effects?", "correct_answer": "Its frequency", "incorrect_answers": ["Its mass", "Its speed", "Its volume"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1979 comedy-drama movie Being There ends with this quote.", "correct_answer": "Life is a state of mind", "incorrect_answers": ["Nothing is as difficult as living", "Stay with me forever", "Being these is never impossible"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Parrots are considered the most intelligent birds on the planet along with these birds.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Ravens", "Jays", "Crows"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Earl Holliman starred in a weekly western series titled Hotel de Paree.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the main Internet computer located?", "correct_answer": "Nowhere", "incorrect_answers": ["Greenwich, England", "New York, New York, USA", "Geneva, Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Toronto, Canada the raccoon has become a great urban pest, only exceeded by the Gray Squirrel.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Dirty Dancing, Penny gets pregnant by Johnny.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]